[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "01_SoleSurvivor",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "01_SoleSurvivor_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "01_SoleSurvivor2",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@01_SoleSurvivor_title",
        "Description": "@01_SoleSurvivor_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_SoleSurvivor_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_SoleSurvivor_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_SoleSurvivor_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_SoleSurvivor_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "01_SoleSurvivor2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "01_SoleSurvivor2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": null,
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@01_SoleSurvivor_title",
        "Description": "@01_SoleSurvivor2_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@prompt_DEFAULT",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "",
        "InProgressResponse": "",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_getoffbeach_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_ww",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@01_GetOffBeach_title",
        "Description": "@01_GetOffBeach_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_skinningknife_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_skinningknife_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_skinningknife_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_GetOffBeach_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_getoffbeach",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_getoffbeach_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "!S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "S_getoffbeach_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@01_GetOffBeach_title",
        "Description": "@01_GetOffBeach_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_skinningknife_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_skinningknife_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_skinningknife_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_GetOffBeach_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_skinningknife",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_skinningknife_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_skinningknife",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_ww",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_skinningknife_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_skinningknife_title",
        "Description": "@01_skinningknife_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_skinningknife_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_skinningknife_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_skinningknife_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_skinningknife_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_skinningknife",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 1,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_skinningknife_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_skinningknife_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_getoffbeach_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_skinningknife_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_skinningknife_title",
        "Description": "@01_skinningknife_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_skinningknife_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_skinningknife_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_skinningknife_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_skinningknife_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_boarfeast",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_boarfeast_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarfeast",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_skinningknife",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_boarfeast_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_boarfeast_title",
        "Description": "@01_boarfeast_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_boarfeast_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_boarfeast_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_boarfeast_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_boarfeast_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_boarfeast",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_boarfeast_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_boarfeast_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_skinningknife_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_boarfeast_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_boarfeast_title",
        "Description": "@01_boarfeast_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_boarfeast_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_boarfeast_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_boarfeast_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_boarfeast_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_crewmates",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_crewmates_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_crewmates",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_boarfeast",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_crewmates_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_crewmates_title",
        "Description": "@01_crewmates_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_crewmates_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_crewmates_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_crewmates_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_crewmates_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_crewmates",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 2,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_crewmates_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_crewmates_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_boarfeast_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_crewmates_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_crewmates_title",
        "Description": "@01_crewmates_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_crewmates_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_crewmates_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_crewmates_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_crewmates_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_survivors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_survivors_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceWW_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_survivors",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_crewmates",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_06_survivors_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_survivors_title",
        "Description": "@01_recoveritems_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_survivors_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_survivors_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_survivors_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_survivors_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_survivors",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_survivors_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceMB_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_survivors_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_crewmates_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_survivors_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_survivors_title",
        "Description": "@01_recoveritems_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_survivors_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_survivors_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_survivors_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_survivors_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_pillageship",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_pillageship_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_pillageship",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_survivors",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_06_pillageship_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_pillageship_title",
        "Description": "@01_pillageship_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_pillageship_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_pillageship_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_pillageship_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_pillageship_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_pillageship",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 3,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_pillageship_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_GraceMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_pillageship_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_survivors_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_pillageship_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_pillageship_title",
        "Description": "@01_pillageship_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_pillageship_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_pillageship_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_pillageship_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_pillageship_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_recoveritems",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_recoveritems_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_recoveritems",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_pillageship",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_06_recoveritems_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_recoveritems_title",
        "Description": "@01_recoveritems_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_recoveritems_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_recoveritems_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_recoveritems_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_recoveritems_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_recoveritems",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 4,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_recoveritems_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_recoveritems_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_pillageship_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_recoveritems_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_recoveritems_title",
        "Description": "@01_recoveritems_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_recoveritems_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_recoveritems_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_recoveritems_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_recoveritems_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_demonstorm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_demonstorm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_recoveritems",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_demonstorm_title",
        "Description": "@01_demonstorm_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_demonstorm_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_demonstorm_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_demonstorm_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_demonstorm_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_demonstorm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_demonstorm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_recoveritems_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_demonstorm_title",
        "Description": "@01_demonstorm_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_demonstorm_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_demonstorm_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_demonstorm_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_demonstorm_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_demonstorm2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_demonstorm2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseWW_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm2",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_demonstorm2_title",
        "Description": "@01_demonstorm2_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_demonstorm2_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_demonstorm2_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_demonstorm2_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_demonstorm2_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_demonstorm2",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_demonstorm2_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "01_ReeseMB_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_demonstorm2_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_demonstorm2_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_demonstorm2_title",
        "Description": "@01_demonstorm2_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_demonstorm2_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_demonstorm2_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_demonstorm2_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_demonstorm2_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "06_raisealarm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "06_raisealarm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "06_MarcelDupont01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_raisealarm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_raisealarm_title",
        "Description": "@01_raisealarm_description_06",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_raisealarm_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_raisealarm_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_raisealarm_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_raisealarm_complete_06",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "12_raisealarm",
        "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "12_raisealarm_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "12_SerPayneBennett",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_introtosettlement",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "01_raisealarm_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@01_raisealarm_title",
        "Description": "@01_raisealarm_description_12",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@01_raisealarm_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@01_raisealarm_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@01_raisealarm_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@01_raisealarm_complete_12",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "0625_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "0625_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistWW_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 6,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles_ww",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "0625_0101_truffles_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0425_0101_truffles_title",
        "Description": "@0425_0101_truffles_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "1225_0101_truffles",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": 5,
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "1225_0101_d_00_container_truffles",
        "NpcDestinationId": "0425_HerbalistMB_Town",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": 12,
        "AchievementId": "S_truffles_mb",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "S_demonstorm2_mb",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "1225_0101_truffles_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "@0425_0101_truffles_title",
        "Description": "@0425_0101_truffles_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@0425_0101_truffles_start_prompt",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@0425_0101_truffles_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": null,
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
